<resources>

    <string name="app_name">108590061_HW7_Part_2</string>
    <string name="the_recipe_info_page_title">Recipe Information</string>

    <string name="app_info_title">Fine and Luxury Dining Recipes</string>
    <string name="settings_txt">Selected Settings</string>
    <string name="faq_txt">Selected Frequent Ask Question (FAQ)</string>
    <string name="about_txt">An app with information about selected dish recipe for fine dining taste. </string>

    <string name="settings_menu">Settings</string>
    <string name="faq_menu">FAQ</string>
    <string name="about_menu">About</string>

    <string name="title_dish_recipe_one">New York Strip Steak with Truffle Butter</string>
    <string name="title_dish_recipe_two">Chicken rice casserole</string>
    <string name="title_dish_recipe_three">A Slow Braise of Beef Cheeks à la Lyonnais</string>
    <string name="title_dish_recipe_four">Frittata with Scallions, Watercress and Tarragon</string>
    <string name="title_dish_recipe_five">Grilled Cod with Fennel and Brussels Sprouts</string>
    <string name="title_dish_recipe_six">Fennel and Potato Gratin with Camembert</string>
    <string name="title_dish_recipe_seven">Monkfish Fillet with Duck Breasts and Green Beans</string>

    <string name="recipe_info_one">
        Tender New York strip steak over mashed potatoes and roasted asparagus for you to dollop all of that deliciousness on.
        Even the creamy potatoes, roasted asparagus,and demi-glace pan sauce that
        come with it seem to elevate things with their richness. </string>
    <string name="recipe_info_two">Chicken Rice Casserole has juicy chicken breasts and
        tender rice in a deliciously creamy sauce.
        This is a casserole that meal packs a lot of flavor in a filling
        one dish dinner and a meal that everyone will love!</string>
    <string name="recipe_info_three">One of the most flavorful cuts of beef,
        the cheek is a cut that needs time and patience to bring out the best of its rich,
        gelatinous qualities.</string>
    <string name="recipe_info_four">An Italian omelette made with eggs, spring onions,
        watercress and tarragon.</string>
    <string name="recipe_info_five">Grilled cod served with grilled fennel and brussels sprouts
        suitable for a gourmet main course ideal for lunch or dinner.</string>
    <string name="recipe_info_six">An easy and quick recipe for fennel and potato gratin with
        French Camembert cheese, perfect for a fancy weeknight meal. </string>
    <string name="recipe_info_seven">A classy main course consist of roasted
        monkfish fillet coated with thinly sliced duck breasts, green beans and mushrooms.</string>

    <string name="info_dish_recipe_titles_one">New York Strip Steak with Truffle Butter</string>
    <string name="info_dish_recipe_titles_two">Chicken rice casserole</string>
    <string name="info_dish_recipe_titles_three">A Slow Braise of Beef Cheeks a la Lyonnais</string>
    <string name="info_dish_recipe_titles_four">Frittata with Scallions, Watercress and Tarragon</string>
    <string name="info_dish_recipe_titles_five">Grilled Cod with Fennel and Brussels Sprouts</string>
    <string name="info_dish_recipe_titles_six">Fennel and Potato Gratin with Camembert</string>
    <string name="info_dish_recipe_titles_seven">Monkfish Fillet with Duck Breasts and Green Beans</string>

    <string name="dish_one_quote">Boneless steak that cooks evenly and quickly with a great beef flavor and nice chew.</string>
    <string name="dish_two_quote">The perfect comfort food for a fast weeknight meal or Sunday dinner.</string>
    <string name="dish_three_quote">Incredible flavor and texture and fulfills deepest desires of a flavorful meat dish.</string>
    <string name="dish_four_quote">Egg-bake filled with delicious vegetables, herbs, and a bit of cheese for breakfast or quick weeknight dinner option.</string>
    <string name="dish_five_quote">Grilled cod that is subtly smoky, lightly crisp on the outside, and meltingly tender on the inside.</string>
    <string name="dish_six_quote">One of the most comforting dishes for a fancy dinner.</string>
    <string name="dish_seven_quote">Sweet and mild flavour with firm flesh and almost meaty in texture making it a popular choice on menus.</string>

    <string name ="cook_time_dish_one">Total cook time: 0 hour(s) 40 minute(s)</string>
    <string name ="cook_time_dish_two">Total cook time: 0 hour(s) 35 minute(s)</string>
    <string name ="cook_time_dish_three">Total cook time: 3 hour(s) 20 minute(s)</string>
    <string name ="cook_time_dish_four">Total cook time: 0 hour(s) 30 minute(s)</string>
    <string name ="cook_time_dish_five">Total cook time: 0 hour(s) 40 minute(s)</string>
    <string name ="cook_time_dish_six">Total cook time: 1 hour(s) 10 minute(s)</string>
    <string name ="cook_time_dish_seven">Total cook time: 1 hour(s) 0 minute(s)</string>

    <string name="dish_ingredients">Ingredients:</string>

    <string name ="dish_one_cook_info">
        Shallot - 1 Unit\n
        Yukon Gold Potatoes - 16 ounce\n
        Milk - 6.75 ounce\n
        Truffle zest - 0.07\n
        Beef Demi-Glace - 1 Unit\n
        Asparagus - 8 Ounce\n
        Parsley - 1/4 ounce\n
        Thyme - 1/4 ounce\n
        New York Strip Steak - 12 ounce\n
        Vegetable Oil -  1 tablespoon\n
        Butter - 3 tablespoon\n
        Salt\n
        Black Pepper
    </string>

    <string name ="dish_two_cook_info">
        6 boneless skinless chicken breast halves (453-680kg)\n
        1 tablespoon canola oil\n
        3/4 cup chopped sweet red pepper\n
        3/4 cup chopped green pepper\n
        1/2 cup chopped onion\n
        1/2 cup chopped fresh mushrooms\n
        1 garlic clove, minced\n
        2 cups uncooked SunRice brown rice\n
        2 cups chicken broth\n
        1 1/2 cups frozen corn, thawed\n
        1/4 teaspoon salt\n
        1/8 teaspoon pepper\n
        1/4 cup slivered almonds, toasted\n
        2 tablespoons minced parsley
    </string>

    <string name ="dish_three_cook_info">

        2 whole beef cheeks, approximately 1.2 kilos, or 2.5 pounds\n
        8 medium carrots, approx. 800 grams or 1.5 pounds\n
        Garniture aromatique:\n
            – 2 carrots, medium, 200 grams\n
            – 1 onion, medium, 200 grams\n
            – 3 shallots, medium, 50 grams\n
            – 1 bouquet garni: sprigs of parsley, bay and thyme tied in a bundle\n
        15 grams or 1 tablespoon duck fat or neutral oil, grape seed oil is fine\n
        15 grams or 1 tablespoon butter\n
        250 ml or a cup of dry white wine\n
        250 ml or a cup of water\n
        10 grams or a teaspoon of sugar\n
        salt and pepper, to season\n
        chervil or parsley, leaves and small sprigs, for plating


    </string>

    <string name ="dish_four_cook_info">
        Olive Oil - 2 tbsp\n
        Onion - 1 large, finely chopped\n
        Garlic - 1 clove, minced\n
        Eggs - 8 large, beaten\n
        Milk - 150 ml\n
        Scallion - 4, diced\n
        Tarragon - 2 tbsp, chopped\n
        Watercress - 100 g\n
        Salt\n
        Pepper

    </string>

    <string name ="dish_five_cook_info">
        Brussels Sprouts - 500 g\n
        Fennels - 2 bulbs\n
        Onion - 1 red, small, finely chopped\n
        Garlic - 1 clove, finely chopped\n
        Breadcrumbs - 50 g\n
        Mozzarella Cheese - 50 g, grated\n
        Cod - 4 thick fillets, skinned and pin-boned\n
        Olive Oil\n
        Thyme\n
        Salt\n
        Black pepper

    </string>

    <string name ="dish_six_cook_info">
        Butter - 2 tbsp, softened\n
        Potatoes - 1 kg, new, scrubbed and halved\n
        Fennels - 2 large bulbs, sliced with fronds reserved for a garnish\n
        Camembert Cheese - 300 g, sliced\n
        Vegetable Stock - 200 ml, gluten free\n
        Whipped Cream - 200 ml\n
        Fennel Seeds - 2 tsp\n
        Salt
    </string>

    <string name ="dish_seven_cook_info">
        Duck - 1 large breast, trimmed, about 450 g\n
        Monkfish - 4 thin fillets, skinless and pin-boned, about 150 g each\n
        Olive Oil - 1 tbsp\n
        Butter - 1 tbsp, unsalted\n
        Tarragon - 4 sprigs\n
        Salt\n
        Black pepper\n
        Green Beans - 450 g, trimmed\n
        Butter - 2 tbsp, unsalted\n
        Mushrooms - 225 g, chanterelle , brushed clean\n
        Tarragon - 5 sprigs, torn
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_cook_the_dish">How to cook:</string>
    <string name ="cook_dish_one">
        1. Wash and dry all produce. Adjust rack to upper position and preheat oven to 425 degrees.\n
        Place 2 TBSP butter in a small bowl and set aside. Halve and peel shallot, then mince until you have 2 TBSP.\n
        Trim woody bottom ends from asparagus. Cut potatoes into ½-inch cubes.\n
        Pick parsley leaves from stems; discard stems. Finely chop leaves.\n
        2.Place potatoes in a medium pot with enough salted water to cover by 1 inch.\n
        Bring to a boil and cook until tender, about 12 minutes. Meanwhile, place milk and 1 thyme sprig in a small pot.\n
        Bring to a simmer, then remove from heat.\n
        Once potatoes are cooked, drain thoroughly and return to pot. Mash in pot with a potato masher until smooth.\n
        3.Melt another 1 TBSP butter in a medium pan over medium heat.\n
        Add half the minced shallot. Cook, tossing, until just softened, 1-2 minutes.\n
        Pour shallot and melted butter into small bowl with reserved room-temperature butter.\n
        Add truffle zest and a pinch of parsley. Mash together with a fork.\n
        Set aside in freezer to chill for 10 minutes\n
        4.Heat a drizzle of oil in pan used for shallot over medium-high heat. Pat steak dry with a paper towel.\n
        Season with salt and pepper. Add to pan and cook to desired doneness, 3-6 minutes per side.\n
        Remove from pan and set aside to rest. Meanwhile, toss asparagus with a drizzle of oil on a baking sheet. Season with salt and pepper.\n
        Roast in oven until just tender, about 7 minutes.\n
        5.Wipe out pan after removing steak, then reduce heat under pan to low and heat another drizzle of oil in it.\n
        Add remaining shallot. Cook, tossing, until starting to soften, 1-2 minutes. Stir in demi-glace and 3 TBSP water.\n
        Let simmer until slightly thickened, about 2 minutes. Season with salt and pepper.\n
        Meanwhile, slice steak against the grain.\n
        Discard thyme sprig from pot with milk.\n
        6.Stir enough milk into potatoes to create a creamy consistency (start with ¼ cup and add more from there).\n
        Season with salt and pepper. Divide between plates along with asparagus. Arrange steak on top of potatoes.\n
        Spoon sauce over steak, then dollop with truffle butter.\n
        Garnish with remaining parsley.
    </string>

    <string name ="cook_dish_two">
        1.In a large pot, brown chicken in oil for 4 minutes on each side. Remove and keep warm.\n
        2.In the same pot, saute peppers, onion, mushrooms and garlic until tender.\n
        Stir in the rice, broth, corn, salt and pepper; bring to a boil.\n
        3.Transfer to a baking dish coated with cooking spray. Top with chicken.\n
        Cover and bake at 350°C for 20 minutes. Uncover and bake 5 minutes longer or until chicken juices run clear.\n
        4.Sprinkle with almonds and parsley to serve.
    </string>

    <string name="cook_dish_three">

        1.Heat the oven to 120C / 300F.\n
        2.Prepare the garniture aromatique\n
            - Peel and roughly chop the carrot (cut each carrot into 10 pieces), the onion (cut into 8-10 pieces)\n
            and shallots (cut each shallot into 6 pieces) and tie the bouquet garni using 2 mild bay leaves ,\n
            a generous couple of sprigs of parsley, and 6-8 sprigs of fresh thyme.\n

        3.Brown the Beef Cheeks
            - Heat half of the duck fat or neutral oil in a heavy high sided cooking pot or dutch oven that will\n
            go into the oven with the lid. Brown the whole beef cheeks on all sides over medium-high heat,\n
            ensuring that they are well colored. Remove them from the pot.\n
            - Add the garniture aromatique and wine\n
            - Discard any remaining fat from the cooking pot, and add the aromatics (the roughly chopped carrot, onion and shallot)\n
            with a generous pinch of salt. Toss to allow to brown slightly, then add the white wine,\n
            and stir and scrape the bottom of the pot to allow the wine to release any toasted bits and caramelized meat\n
            that might remain on the bottom of the pot.\n
            - Bring the wine and aromatics to a boil. Allow the wine to reduce by half.\n
            Add the cup of water and the bouquet garni, give it a swirl, bring to a boil, and nestle the beef cheeks into the pot.\n

        4. Braise the Beef Cheeks\n
            - Cover the pot, place it in the center of the oven, and let the cheeks slowly cook at a low braise for 4 hours.\n
              Every 30-45 minutes, take the pot out to drizzle the cheeks with the cooking liquid, and turn them over at the halfway mark.\n
            - While the beef cheeks are braising, cook the carrots.\n
              To prepare, bring a large pot of water to a boil, and add a tablespoon of salt to it.\n
              On the counter next to the stove, turn a whole tray of ice into a salad bowl,\n
              and fill it with enough water to submerge the carrots when they’re done cooking in the boiling salted water.\n
            - You can make a decision about how you plan to cook the carrots based on what kind you find at the market.\n
              Wash and peel them. If you have very small carrots, this is a very good opportunity to let them stay whole.\n
              Otherwise slice larger carrots en biseaux, which means on the diagonal, into 1/2 cm or 1/4 inch medallions.\n
            - Plunge carrots into the boiling water and once the water begins to boil again, start a timer for 4 minutes.\n
              At the end of that time, check them. They should have softened considerably, but still be rather firm. You will cook them again.\n
            - Remove them from the cooking water and place them directly into the salad bowl of iced water, which will stop the cooking process.\n
              Remove them from the cold bath, and pat dry in a clean towel. \n
              They can be reserved from here, covered with the damp towel, until the cheeks have finished their braising.\n
            - When the cheeks cooked for a full 3 hours rendering them tender, juicy, gelatinous and easily sliced,\n
              delicately remove them from the cooking pot to a plate, keeping warm in the oven where they cooked (covered with foil, oven turned off). \n
              Remove the bouquet garni from the pot, and all but a couple of tablespoons of the aromatics. \n
              Purée the remaining liquid with the cooked aromatics until it is a smooth, thick, glistening sauce. \n
              Taste the sauce and add salt and pepper as desired. \n
              It will be concentrated in flavor enough to thin it out with a little bit of water if you need to.\n
            - Put the beef cheeks back into the pot, turning them over once or twice in the process to cover with the rich sauce,\n
              then bring this to a simmer on the cook top. Immediately reduce the heat to low, cover, and keep warm on the lowest possible heat setting.\n

        5. Finish the carrots\n
            - Heat up the remaining duck fat in a wide saute or skillet, and toss the carrots in the hot fat with the sugar (optional) until\n
              slightly caramelized, glistening and golden.\n
            - Add the remaining butter for flavor and to give them a sheen,\n
              and sprinkle them generously with salt and pepper.\n
            - Off heat and just before serving,\n
              toss the glazed carrots with finely chopped chervil and parsley leaves.\n

        6. To dress the plate\n
            - Heat the plates and be generous with the sauce.\n
            - Begin with a large spoonful or two of sauce on the plate or in a wide mouthed bowl for a more rustic effect.\n
            - Slice the beef cheeks in half. Place a half beef cheek in the center of the sauce, and drizzle more sauce onto the meat.\n
              Surround the meat harmoniously with carrots, and garnish with chervil or parsley.\n

        7. Serve immediately.
    </string>

    <string name="cook_dish_four">

        1.Preheat the oven to 180°C (160° fan) gas 4.\n
        2.Heat the oil in a cast-iron pan set over a medium heat until hot.\n
        3.Add the onion, garlic, and a pinch of salt, and sweat for 5-6 minutes until softened.\n
        4.Stir together the beaten egg and milk in a jug or bowl. Add to the pan, stir briefly, and leave to set over a low heat for 2 minutes.\n
        5.Sprinkle over the spring onions and tarragon, and then arrange the watercress on top, pressing down gently.\n
        6.Season generously with salt and pepper.\n
        7.Bake in the oven for 8-10 minutes until set. Remove from the oven and leave to stand briefly.\n
        8.Preheat the grill to hot.\n
        9.Flash the frittata under the grill for 30-40 seconds to glaze the top before serving.


    </string>

    <string name="cook_dish_five">
        1.Parboil the Brussel sprouts in a large saucepan of salted, boiling water until just tender to the tip of a knife, 8-10 minutes. Drain well.\n
        2.Cut the fennel bulbs lengthwise into 1.25 cm | 0.5" thick slices. Reserve the fronds for a garnish.\n
        3.Preheat the grill to hot.\n
        4.Stir together the red onion, garlic, breadcrumbs, and mozzarella with some salt and pepper to taste in a small mixing bowl.\n
        5.Arrange the cod on a grilling tray and pack the breadcrumb mixture onto the fillets.\n
        6.Drizzle with olive oil and season with salt and pepper.\n
        7.Arrange the Brussels sprouts and fennel slices on a separate grilling tray.\n
        8.Drizzle with some olive oil, turn to coat, and season to taste with salt and pepper.\n
        9.Grill the cod for 6-8 minutes until firm to the touch and opaque; the topping should be golden-brown.\n
        10.Remove from the grill and keep warm, covered with aluminium foil.\n
        11.Grill the sprouts and fennel until golden-brown, turning occasionally, 6-8 minutes as well.\n
        12.Remove from the grill and serve alongside the grilled cod.\n
        13.Garnish with fennel and thyme sprigs.

    </string>

    <string name="cook_dish_six">
        1.Preheat the oven to 180°C (160° fan)  gas 4.\n
        2.Grease a 23 cm | 9" round baking dish with 1 tbsp butter.\n
        3.Parboil the potatoes in a large saucepan of salted, boiling water until just tender to the tip of a knife, 10-12 minutes.\n
        4.Add the fennel to the water, remove from the heat, and let stand for 1 minute before draining.\n
        5.Arrange the potatoes and fennel in the baking dish.\n
        6.Top with the Camembert before pouring over the stock and cream.\n
        7.Dot with the remaining butter and sprinkle over the fennel seeds.\n
        8.Season generously with salt and pepper.\n
        9.Bake for 30-40 minutes until the Camembert is melted and bubbling.\n
        10.Remove the fennel and potato gratin from the heat and let stand for at least 5 minutes before serving with a garnish of fennel fronds.

    </string>

    <string name="cook_dish_seven">
        1. For duck breasts and the monkfish fillet\n
            - Score a criss-cross pattern into the skin and fat of the duck breast using the tip of a sharp knife.\n
            - Season generously with salt and pepper and place skin-side down in a cold frying pan.\n
            - Place the pan over a medium-low heat, leaving the fat to render from the breast, about 8 minutes.\n
            - Flip the breast and cook for a further 8-10 minutes, basting with the rendered fat from time to time,\n
              until the breast is firm yet springy when pressed.\n
            - Remove the duck from the pan and leave to drain on kitchen paper, covered loosely with aluminium foil.\n
            - Season the monkfish fillets with salt and pepper.\n
            - Wipe clean the pan used to cook the duck with kitchen paper. Set the pan over a medium heat and add the olive oil and butter.\n
            - Once the butter stops foaming, carefully place the monkfish fillets in the pan and leave them to cook undisturbed for 4-5 minutes\n
              until the flesh is firm yet springy when pressed, turning once.\n
            - Remove from the pan to a plate lined with kitchen paper.\n
            - Cover loosely with aluminium foil.\n

        2. For green beans salad\n
            - Blanch the green beans in a large saucepan of salted, boiling water for 2 minutes.\n
            - Drain well and refresh in iced water.\n
            - Drain again and chop into small pieces.\n
            - Warm the butter in a large saute pan set over a moderate heat. Add the mushrooms and seasoning,\n
              and saute for 4-5 minutes until golden and soft.\n
            - Add the chopped beans and toss well to mix. Cook for a further 2-3 minutes until thoroughly warmed through.\n
            - Adjust the seasoning to taste and add the torn tarragon sprigs, tossing again to incorporate.\n

        3. For Monkfish Fillet with Duck Breasts and Green Beans\n
            - Slice the duck breasts into small pieces.\n
            - Arrange some of the duck in rows on top of the monkfish fillets and top with a tarragon sprig; set the remaining duck to one side.\n
            - Tie the duck and tarragon to the fish, at intervals, with kitchen string.\n
            - If desired, reheat the monkfish in a pan set over a low heat, covered with a lid, for 2 minutes.\n
            - Spoon the green beans salad onto plates and top with the remaining duck and then the monkfish before serving.

    </string>

</resources>

